How are you friends and welcome to a dhamakad video, so
friends,
first of all think important factors from Lombard's side, let's
talk about market cap, the
market cap of 6000054 course
is 1233 of the stock,
1370 and loss of 1050,
after doing the P of the stock, it is 35 and you can see that
here it is 213, you can see the dividend here, it
is very low,
0.81%, let's talk about sir, there
is RC of 21.2%, you can see it here,
friends, you can see here,
you can see here, the dividend has been
issued by the company, which is 55% which means
₹550, here the company has also issued the record date
12 6 2013,
you must join the gram channel,
I will update them every month,
you must join that telegram channel, we will meet
in the next dhamakad video, till then bye friends,
thank you